开萝尔:没有参加,因为我有其他事做.
Carol: So, maybe I didn't go to the party because I had something else to do.
也许我觉得更有趣的不是昨晚和一帮年轻人玩.
Maybe I had more fun last night than any teenager should be allowed to have.
黛比:可能是这样,不过昨天的晚会,
Debbie: Yea, anyway, it was the greatest party I have ever been to and
我认为确实棒极了,你没去参加?
you missed it!
开萝尔:你把晚会说的那么棒,
Carol: You're just saying it was a great party cause some guy probably
一定是有人请你跳舞.
asked you to dance.
黛比:对,瑞克·莱文!.
Debbie: Yea.Rick Levin.
友人:嗨开萝尔!嗨黛比!
Friend: Hi Carol.Hi Deb.
黛比:我在说昨天的晚会太好了.
Debbie: I was just telling Carol what she missed last night!
友人:这是我一生中所遇到的最糟糕的晚会.
Friend: Absolutely the worst party I have ever been to!
黛比:什么?
Debbie: What?
友人:在整个晚会上请我跳舞的,
Friend: The only guy who asked me to dance the entire night was that wimp,
只有瑞克·莱文那孬种.
Rick Levin.
黛比:可我认为他是很帅的一个人.
Debbie: You don't think he's a fox?
友人:毫无自尊心,他跟谁都跳.
Friend: The man has no self-esteem.He'll dance with anybody.
开萝尔:我昨晚过得很开心.鲍比一直陪着我.
Carol: Speaking of last night, I spent the entire evening with Bobby.
黛比:怎么了?
Debbie: So?
友人:了不起.是一起复习?
Friend: Big deal.So you were studying.
开萝尔:哦对,当然是在复习.
Carol: Oh, yea.Sure, ok.We were studying.Believe that.
友人:你说什么啊?
Friend: What are you saying?
开萝尔:我什么也不想说了.
Carol: Well, I really shouldn't say anymore.
黛比和朋友:开萝尔!:
Debbie and Friend: Carol!
开萝尔:不过比汽车礼仪表盘上的灯光,是看不了多少书的,
Carol: Well, let's just say that it was hard to read by the light of the
前面那辆车又是停在一条黑暗的巷子里.
dashboard of his car, which by the way, was parked out on Old Johnson Rd.
卢沃克教练:早上好同学们.我今天早上醒来的时候,
Coach Luvok: Good morning, people.
脑瓜里钻出一个新点子出来,是做梦时想出来的,
Class, I woke up this morning with a renewed interest in the teaching
我本来想在课堂上讨论格斯蒂的书,
profession.It came to me in my sleep.
一起互相交谈看法,过来一下,
I'd planned a discussion period on the Great Gatsby assignment.
不,干脆测验.
A frank, open exchange of perceptions.And then I thought, Nah.'Pop quiz!
开萝尔:要测验?
Carol: A quiz?
卢沃克教练:要写一篇文章,
Coach Luvok: Essay questions, complete answers.
要写得长一点,
None of you chuckleheads gets away with those two word answers like,
要详细的描述格斯蒂的含义.
Gatsby's loaded.
Friend: Carol, quick!Tell me what the Great Gatsby's about
开萝尔:不知道.
Carol: I don't know!
友人:得了吧,开萝尔!我知道你什么都懂!
Friend: Come on, Carol!You always know!You're always prepared!
开萝尔:告诉你了,我书都没看.
Carol: I told you, I didn't study.
黛比:为什么?
Debbie: Well, why not?
开萝尔:鲍比跟我玩了一个晚上.
Carol: Because I was making out with Bobby!
格雷丝:想不到今天的事,最后一次谢医生,
Grace: I, uh, I can't believe this is our final session, Dr.Seaver.
我已经好多了,谢谢你.
But I feel strong.I feel ready.Thank you.
杰森:不,不,
Jason: No, no, no, no.Thank you, Grace.You've worked very hard.
谢谢你科尔斯,你非常努力,只不过是向你提供咨询和建议.
I just guided you, offered some observations and insights.
格雷丝:这点你说的也是,
Grace: Well, I wouldn't have been able to Oh.
哦对了,我发现要是不在这儿,
I just realized by not coming here,
也许每周能省下一百块钱.
I'm gonna save a hundred dollars every week.
杰森:那主要并不在于钱,
Jason: Well, I'm not in this primarily for the money, you know.
而在于治病救人.
I like helping people.
格雷丝:那不妨把钱全部退给我.
Grace: So maybe you could give me all my money back.
杰森:你疯了.说什么话?
Jason: What're you, crazy?Bad choice of words.
电视节目:乍得美丽的风光就像新婚之夜一样让你兴奋.
TV: Chad, touching you now is just as exciting as it was on our wedding night.
杰森:Ben你在干什么?
Jason: Ben, what're you doing?
本:停下来轻松一下.
Ben: Unwinding after a hard day.
杰森:你到外面去轻松.
Jason: Well, unwind outside!
本:哦爸爸.
Ben: But, Dad!
杰森:去.
Jason: Go!
电视节目:我告诉你,我不是艾特,
TV: Dawn, I have to tell you.I am not Chad!I'm his twin brother!
我是他双胞胎的弟弟.我没说错,你嫁错人了.
That's right!You've married the wrong man!
迈克:嗨爸爸!
Mike: Hey, Dad!
杰森:嗨儿子!是本留下的.
Jason: Hi, son.Ben left this on.
迈克:爸你常跟我讲,
Mike: Hey, Dad.Remember how you told me if I studied really hard and applied
只要努力学习就保证我得好成绩.
myself I'd get dynamite grades?
杰森:是.
Jason: Yea.
迈克:你说的对极了,你看,这是A和C-.
Mike: Well, you were so right!Look at this.A C minus.
杰森:我该祝贺你了迈克,你这次经过努力,
Jason: Well, congratulations, Mike.
总算不再是全班最后一名了.
Must feel great to finally not be the guy with the lowest grade in class.
迈克:爸爸我没这么讲.
Mike: Well, I didn't say that.
开萝尔:你总算回来了.
Carol: Thank God, you're here.
迈克:和我说话?
Mike: You talkin' to me?
开萝尔:嗨!我要你帮个忙,你跟我说说考试不及格怎么办?
Carol: I need your help.I need to know how to live with being a failure.
迈克:开萝尔你就别来逗我了.
Mike: Oh, get out of my way.
开萝尔:迈克我测验没有及格.
Carol: Mike, I flunked a test.
迈克:那倒不坏.
Mike: Yea, right.
开萝尔:那我全优的记录被玷污了?
Carol: My perfect record is blemished.
迈克:玷污了?啊,
Mike: Blemished?Oh, no, no.
不,不,你是想拿我来解解闷是吗?
You're setting me up for some kind of zit joke, right?
开萝尔:是真的,我得了f.
Carol: No, I'm serious.I got an F.
迈克:给我看.
Mike: Let me see it.
开萝尔:卷子还没有发下来,可我心里明白,
Carol: Well, I don't have the test back yet.
测验时我一点都答不出.
But all the while I was taking it, I didn't know one single answer.
迈克:就是说你已经肯定不及格了?
Mike: So, we're talking an official F here?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes!
迈克:肯定不会错?
Mike: I can count on this.
开萝尔:要不然我来找你干嘛?
Carol: Oh, what am I talking to you for?
我认为这是我一生中最倒霉的事情.
This is absolutely the worst thing that could ever happen.
迈克:我看不见得.
Mike: Not really.
开萝尔:你成绩竟然比我好.
Carol: You got a better grade than I did?
迈克:别担心开萝尔,爸爸妈妈你不用去讲,
Mike: Hey, don't worry Carol.
我会去的.
You don't have to tell Mom and Dad you went belly up.I will.
开萝尔:迈克爸爸妈妈要是知道了,他们会伤心的,
Carol: Mike.Mom an Dad could seriously be hurt by this.
他们年龄大了.
They're not young people.
迈克:早知道是这样,
Mike: Well, maybe you should've thought of that before you came in here
刚才就不应该对我把什么都抖出来,
spilling your guts out to me.
这样重大的新闻,可以保得了密吗?
I mean, did you really expect me to keep such great news private?
你还不道我迈克·西维尔是什么样的人?
I mean, come on, Carol!This is Mike Seaver you're dealing with here!
麦琪:嗨本!
Maggie: Hi Benny!
本:嗨!她在!
Ben: Hi.She's here!
麦琪:这是怎么回事?
Maggie: What's this about?
本:不知道,开萝尔叫我一看到你就喊,
Ben: I don't know.
她给我一块钱.
Carol just said it's worth a buck to know the instance you came in.
开萝尔:妈妈坐下,爸爸.
Carol: Mom, sit down.Dad!
麦琪:怎么回事?
Maggie: What's this about?
开萝尔:你坐下.
Carol: Just sit.
麦琪:我可以先脱掉外衣吗?
Maggie: Can I take off my coat first?
开萝尔:如果快点当然可以.那你走,这事不能让你知道.
Carol: If you hurry.Leave, Ben.This isn't for your ears.
本:那么你给我的一块钱呢?
Ben: What about that dollar you owe me?
开萝尔:在我皮夹里藏在楼上.
Carol: It's in my wallet, hidden upstairs
本:我知道藏在哪.
Ben: I know where it is.
麦琪:亲爱的怎么回事?
Maggie: Honey, what is this?
杰森:不知道,重要是内容是什么?
Jason: I don't know.What's the big announcement you wanted to make?
开萝尔:请坐下,好,你就当我是爱你们的.
Carol: You should sit.Now, you both know I love you.
麦琪:哦我的上帝.
Maggie: Oh my goodness!
杰森:亲爱的.
Jason: Honey.
麦琪:你先跟我说,你要声明的事,
Maggie: I just want to know,
是不是跟鲍比有关系?
does this have anything to do with going steady with Bobby?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes?
开萝尔:我犯了个严重的错误.
Carol: I've made a terrible mistake.
杰森:哦上帝.
Jason: Oh my goodness.
麦琪:我就知道一定会出事的.
Maggie: I knew going steady was wrong.
杰森:宝贝我们提醒了你.
Jason: Honey, we've talked about boys.
麦琪:这件事都怪我.
Maggie: I blame myself.
杰森:不,这件事我也有责任.
Jason: No, I'm just as much to blame as you.
麦琪:几时发生的.
Maggie: When did this happen?
开萝尔:今天上语文课的时候.
Carol: Today in English class.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:还是在上课的时候?
Maggie: In English class?Jason!
杰森:等一等,等一等,你和我们说的是一回事吗?
Jason: Wait a minute.We talking about the same thing?
开萝尔:你们说的是什么事?
Carol: Well, what are you talking about?
杰森:你说的是什么事?
Jason: No, what are you talking about?
开萝尔:英语作业,因为跟鲍比在一起所以就没复习.
Carol: Well, my English quiz.I didn't study because I was out with Bobby.
麦琪:我差点都被吓昏了.
Maggie: Boy, you really had us going there.
开萝尔:你们以为是什么?
Carol: What did you think I meant?
杰森:这个问题我看还是别谈算了.
Jason: Nothing I ever want to talk about again.
迈克:你好吗,妈妈.对不起爸爸.
Mike: Hello, Mother.Excuse me, Father.Carol?Oh, excuse me.
开萝尔?哦!我影响你们谈话了.
I'm interrupting something.
麦琪:究竟是什么事情?
Maggie: Now, honey.What's the problem?
开萝尔:今天这一天对我来说是最倒霉的一天,因为没复习,
Carol: This is absolutely the worst day of my academic life.
英语考试不及格,我毁掉全优记录.
I flunked my English quiz.I wasn't prepared and I spoiled my perfect record.
麦琪:亲爱的!你对自己别太苛刻了.
Maggie: Sweetheart, don't be so hard on yourself.
迈克:现在我是不是宣布一件好消息?
Mike: If I might jump in here with some happy news.
杰森:等一会儿Mike,你没必要这样伤心.
Jason: Not now, Mike.Carol, it's not the end of the world.
开萝尔:爸爸不及格我从没有过.
Carol: But Dad, I've never flunked anything.
迈克:爸爸妈妈要是把我们的好成绩贴在这儿呢?
Mike: Uh, Mom.Is this where you put the grades you're so proud of or is
还是放在那?
it the freezer side?
麦琪:你等等迈克,开萝尔谁都会有缺点的.
Maggie: In a minute, Mike.Carol, nobody is perfect.
开萝尔:可我是一个优等生,你们一向为我感到骄傲,说我是好孩子.
Carol: But, don't you see?I was!I was your 4.0 daughter.You both call me that.
杰森:亲爱的看问题要从长远来看,像这种东西.
Jason: Honey, you're losing all perspective here.In time you'll see.
Mike: Speaking of C, I think you'll get a real kick out of this
麦琪:开萝尔你这次是因为没有复习才不及格的.
Maggie: Carol, you didn't study and you got one bad grade.
杰森:这只是几百分之一,那是极小极小的.
Jason: It's one out of hundreds, honey.It's infinitesimal.
麦琪:一次分数并不很重要,重要的是经常的分数.
Maggie: We don't care about one grade.We care about how you do overall.
开萝尔:说得对,
Carol: Yea, you're right.
光为了一次分数我看是没必要这样激动,说到这一点,
I mean, one grade isn't anything to get too excited about.
迈克有重要新闻要宣布.
Speaking of which, I believe Mike has some news.
卢沃克教练:哪一位同学曾经想到过,要产出这么多纸,
Coach Luvok: Has it ever occurred to you people how many trees had to
得砍掉多少棵树?
be murdered to make these sheets of paper?
是我昨晚想到的,
Well, it occurred to me last night when I graded them.
批卷子的时候,那生活不太如意吗?
How do you people live with yourselves?
开萝尔:我想为我昨天考试的成绩道歉,我在这表示今后绝不再发生,
Carol: I would just like to apologize for my performance yesterday and
对不起谢谢.
just say that it will never happen again.I'm ashamed.Thank you.
卢沃克教练:你说什么玩意儿,
Coach Luvok: What the heck are you doing?
你得了这个分数还要道歉,
If you have to apologize for your grade then Horowitz over there has to
其他人我看只好跳大墙了.
shampoo my pit bull.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
卢沃克教练:给你的.其他人的考卷实在是够呛.恶心!
Coach Luvok: Here you go, Seaver.As for the rest of you, you disgust me!
开萝尔:没想到给我一个A+.
Carol: I actually got an A plus!
友人:别再给我演戏了.
Friend: Spare me the dramatics!
开萝尔:不信你瞧.
Carol: No, look at this!
黛比:行了吧,你留着自己欣赏吧.
Debbie: Go ahead.Rub our noses in it.
开萝尔:我真搞不懂,
Carol: I don't know, I guess,
也许我在小学里就念过格斯蒂这本书,也许我不用念也知道,
I must have read Gatsby in elementary school and forgot.
说不定我什么都知道.
Maybe I don't have to read it.Maybe I just know everything.
友人:也许鲍比汽车里的灯比你说的还要亮,
Friend: Yea, well, maybe the dashboard light in Bobby's car is a lot brighter
也许你没坐他的车.
than you said.If you've ever been in his car.
黛比:可能.
Debbie: Yeah!
电视节目:谁说我把你当成哥哥,是你忘了一个,
TV: You say I married the wrong man, but your forgot one thing!
你身上的那块胎记在这儿.
Your strawberry birthmark right there!
迈克:爸爸.
Mike: Dad!
杰森:在这儿迈克,课上的怎么样?
Jason: Yo, Mike!How was school today?
迈克:好,电视好看吗?好.
Mike: Good.How was your soap opera?Great.
开萝尔:我今天怎么样爸爸?
Carol: Isn't it a fantastic day, Dad?
杰森:心情好像不坏.
Jason: Hey, you're in a fine mood.
开萝尔:对,我想和迈克好好谈谈.
Carol: I don't mind being related to Mike today.Mike!
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
开萝尔:迈克我有样东西要给你看.
Carol: I have something to show you!
迈克:我也有样东西要给你看.
Mike: Yea, I got something to show you, too.
开萝尔:迈克你快下来.
Carol: Mike, get down here!
迈克:什么样的东西?
Mike: This better be important.
开萝尔:迈克,测验结果出来啦!
Carol: Mike, I got my test back today.
迈克:哦!好啊.
Mike: Oh, yea?
开萝尔:我看到上面打的分数真是有点,我实在有点.
Carol: Just seeing that grade in writing reminded me of what I am.
迈克:提醒我了.
Mike: Remind me.
开萝尔:我不能!
Carol: I just can't.
迈克:我说过没关系,我是你哥哥.
Mike: Yes, yes you can.Come on, I'm your brother.
开萝尔:好吧,A+,你可别哭.
Carol: A plus!Read it and weep!
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
开萝尔:我的全优记录没被玷污,
Carol: My perfect record isn't blemished!
以后别再我面前得意洋洋的.
Which is more than I can say for your face.
迈克:开萝尔你不是说你没有复习过吗?
Mike: Oh, look.Come on.You said you didn't even study for this.
开萝尔:可有些人并不需要复习.
Carol: Yea, well, some people don't have to study.
迈克:你要我看,
Mike: Let me see that.
这一部小说在读者身上,
The psychological ramifications of Gatsby's predicament are more interesting
所造成的心理效应,远远超出了小说里描述的特定时代和环境,
within the subtext than any within the text itself.
这是什么意思?
What is this supposed to mean?
开萝尔:意思A+.
Carol: It means A plus!
迈克:等等,我觉得你在考卷里说的全是空话,
Mike: Wait a minute.
跟我一样嘛.
Look, you know, you just double talked your way through this.The same as I do.
开萝尔:我没乱写.
Carol: I did not.
迈克:你瞧这儿,
Mike: Ok, look, Carol.
我虽然不懂,可你是这样写的,
I may not know much,
所造成的心理效应完全是空话.
but I know that psychological ramifications doesn't answer anything.
开萝尔:是的,可我认为你连心理都不知道怎么写.
Carol: Yea, well.Yea, well, you can't even spell psychological.
迈克:我能拼写化学肥料.
Mike: So?I can spell fertilizer.
开萝尔:我不该把考卷给你.
Carol: Give me my test back.
迈克:哦,当然,
Mike: Oh, certainly.Oh, certainly.
当然,你要把这份考卷跟别的全优秀放在一起.
I'm sure you're gonna wanna file that with all the
rest of your bogus A pluses
开萝尔:你这话是什么意思?
Carol: And what's that supposed to mean?
迈克:可以说你的全优记录全都是假的.
Mike: Well, if that one's phony then all rest of them could be, too.
开萝尔:我的每一个优秀,都是我努力得来的.
Carol: Yea, well, I've earned every grade that I've ever gotten.
迈克:是吗?你在出汗了.
Mike: Oh, yea?Then why are you sweating?
开萝尔:我没有出汗,我很兴奋,我兴奋得不得了.
Carol: I'm not sweating!I'm glistening!I'm glistening like a pig.
开萝尔:五年级语文,这剧本的语言虽然是十分丰富,但是它的情节比较简单,结尾也有点使读者有一点泄气,所以我认为王子复仇记,不能算是莎士比亚最好的作品之一.胡说.开萝尔我并不同意你的结论,文章写得很好,给你A+,肯定不该得A+.
Carol: Fifth grade English.While the language of the play is truly beautiful and rich, the plot is nonetheless predictable and the ending more than a bit depressing.It is my judgment that Hamlet cannot be considered one of Shakespeare's major efforts.So wrong.Carol, While I may disagree with your conclusion your paper is excellent.A plus.Definitely didn't deserve.
本:开萝尔!妈妈打你了.
Ben: Carol, are you being punished for something?
开萝尔:没有,怎么?
Carol: No, why?
本:因为你吃了晚饭就上来了,
Ben: Well, you've been up here since dinner.
连甜点心也没吃.
And you didn't even eat your dessert.
开萝尔:我是在乎我这一生中,
Carol: Oh, I'm just up here thinking about my whole sham of a life and
究竟有多少是虚伪的?我觉得好像可不是一个好孩子,
what it means.That I'm not really Carol the Brain after all.
我的生活真是毫无意义.
That my life is a meaningless void.
本:你不想吃甜点了?
Ben: So, you don't want your dessert?
开萝尔:你的生活很单纯,是不是Ben?
Carol: Life is so simple for you isn't it, Ben?
本:这决定于你吃不吃你的甜点.
Ben: Depends on whether or not you want your dessert.
开萝尔:进去吧,送给你吃.
Carol: Go ahead.You can have it.
本:谢谢
Ben: Thanks!
开萝尔:本我羡慕你的单纯.
Carol: Ben, I'm glad you're as simple as you are.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
开萝尔:但你知道我不是原来的开萝尔时,
Carol: At least I know you won't change how you feel about me when word
我相信你能够会爱我的.
gets out that I'm not who I seem.
本:那是谁?
Ben: Who are you?
开萝尔:是一贯骗人的人,是一个很痛恨过去的人,
Carol: Somebody who's been living a lie.Somebody who's really tired of it.
是一个决心要改正的人,你听懂了?
Someone who's ready for the truth.Do you understand?
本:我问你,你让我吃甜点是真还是假?
Ben: Just tell me.Were you lying when you said I could have your dessert?
杰森:有人吗?
Jason: Anybody home?
麦琪:我在杰森.
Maggie: I'm here, Jason.
杰森:你今天回来早啊.
Jason: Whoa!You're home early today!
电视节目:当时医院里的那位护士,就是你妈妈.你说什么?
TV: You see, Fawn, that hospital nurse was none other than your mother!
麦琪:你想说什么?
Maggie: What'd you say?
杰森:你为什么回来的那么早?
Jason: Uh, why are you home so early?
麦琪:嘘!等一等
Maggie: Sh-sh.Not now.
电视节目:她就是当时照顾你出生的护士.
TV: And she was the very same nurse who switched us at birth!
麦琪:我还是把它关了吧!
Maggie: I should turn this off.
杰森:哦不,不,我是说你要爱看就看下去.
Jason: No!I mean, if you want to watch that stuff.Go ahead.
麦琪:哦谢谢亲爱的,我也难得这么早回来.
Maggie: Oh, thanks, honey.It's not often I get home early enough to see it.
杰森:今天你是回来的早.
Jason: You are home early today.
电视节目:哦,乍得!你难道看不出,
TV: Oh, Chad.Can't you see that it doesn't matter to me whether you have
我不在乎你有没有在一起,我爱的是你.要知道,
a birthmark or not?It's you I love!But you see my darling.Fawn.
亲爱的,小羊.那个护士,
It can never be!You see, that nurse, your mother, was my mother as well!
你的妈妈,也就是我的妈妈,我是你的哥哥.
I'm your brother!
麦琪:把声音调小点好吗?
Maggie: Do you mind if I turn this down?
杰森:啊?我不看这种东西.
Jason: Huh?I don't watch these things.
麦琪:喂!是卢伯克教练我记得你,开萝尔?
Maggie: Hello?Yes, Coach Luvok.I remember you.Carol?No, that can't be.
这不可能,是的,是的,这当然了,
Yes, yes, of course.Thank you.
谢谢.杰森,开萝尔竟会破坏学校里的财产?
Jason, Carol's been caught vandalizing school property!
麦琪:卢沃克先生.
Maggie: Mr.Luvok.
卢沃克教练:西维尔夫人.西维尔医生.
Coach Luvok: Oh.Mrs.Seaver.Doc.
杰森:开萝尔在哪?
Jason: Where's Carol?
卢沃克教练:有人看着她呢.
Coach Luvok: Ah, in there cooling out.
麦琪:看着她.
Maggie: Cooling out?
卢沃克教练:别担心,我把她的螺丝刀拿走了.
Coach Luvok: Ah, don't worry.I got the screwdriver away from her.
杰森:什么螺丝刀?
Jason: What screwdriver?
格雷丝:我建议我们冷静一点.
Coach Luvok: I suggest we stay in control here.
杰森:那你得向我们说清楚.
Jason: Well, I suggest you tell us what's going on.
卢沃克教练:好,对,
Coach Luvok: Uh, yea, right.Well, here's this kid of yours.
听着你的女儿可真是顶呱呱的响,
Probably the best student I've ever had, I mean,
昨晚看到她以后,
when I look at her and then I look at the rest of the class,
再看看其他学生,就她妈的要吐.
it makes me want to puke.
杰森:卢伯克先生.
Jason: Mr.Luvok
卢沃克教练:就喊我教练.
Coach Luvok: You can call me Coach.
麦琪:卢沃克先生,你刚才……
Maggie: Mr.Luvok, we just...
杰森:教练,你说我们女儿在搞破坏.
Jason: Uh, Coach.You said something about vandalism?
卢沃克教练:不错,我当场抓住的,
Coach Luvok: Oh, yea.I caught her red handed.Let's see.
我看到她用螺丝刀,
Yea, she had a screwdriver and was prying this off the honor society shield
把学校的光荣榜上挖下来,要知道学校的光荣榜是谁也不许随便碰的.
in the quad.Nobody, but nobody, touches the honor society shield.
麦琪:那是她名字.
Maggie: Jason, it's her name.
杰森:她说什么?
Jason: What'd she say when you caught her?
卢沃克教练:她说尊重事实,将获得自由.
Coach Luvok: Well, she said, And by the truth, shall ye be set free.
麦琪:是什么意思?
Maggie: What does that mean?
卢沃克教练:意思是一个人不管怎么都必须诚实,否则就会……
Coach Luvok: Well, it means that a person can be a prisoner of their own lie is and the only way.
麦琪:请问开萝尔什么意思?
Maggie: What did Carol mean?
Coach Luvok: Ah, heck.I don't know.Women never make sense to me, you know
what I mean?Oh, yea and another thing, she comes to me today in class
and tries to get me to change her A plus into a F
麦琪:你说她把f改写成A+?
Maggie: You mean her F into an A plus.
卢沃克教练:不是.
Coach Luvok: No, I don't.
杰森:我们都搞糊涂了.
Jason: Well, that doesn't make any sense.
卢沃克教练:我不是都说了吗?
Coach Luvok: What did I just say?
麦琪:她对我们说她得了个f,我懂,
Maggie: Well, then, why did she tell us she got a F?I know.
你们不懂,因为你们不了解女人.
You don't know because you don't understand women.
卢沃克教练:聪明.
Coach Luvok: Bingo!
麦琪:能不能让我马上见我的女儿.
Maggie: Can we see her now before I lose my temper?
卢沃克教练:行啊,行啊,她干嘛这么火?
Coach Luvok: Sure, sure.Hey, uh, what's she mad at me for?
杰森:这你得去问她自己,我看你永远也不会懂.
Jason: If you have to ask the question, you won't understand the answer.
卢沃克教练:开萝尔肯定有遗传.
Coach Luvok: Now I see where Carol gets it from.
开萝尔:我可以告诉你们,不说你们也会发现对吗?
Carol: Hey, I might as well tell you.
过去那个开萝尔·西维尔,
I mean, you're gonna find out anyway, right?
永远得全优的开萝尔,
The Carol Seaver you've always known, the one who gets the perfect grades,
完全是假的懂吗?讲完了.
well she's a mirage, ok?Case closed.
杰森:不,不,不,不.
Jason: No, no, no, no, no.
麦琪:是不是跟这次不及格的测验有关系?
Maggie: Honey, does this have anything to do with that test you flunked?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
麦琪:我知道了,可是分数并不重要,亲爱的,一次小测验说明不了什么问题.
Maggie: I thought so.Sweetheart, grades don't mean anything.
开萝尔:告诉我为什么.
Carol: Tell me about it.
麦琪:就一次,妈妈我已经全都查过了,十年的成绩,这十年所有的考卷我都查过了.
Maggie: You can't let one dinky little quiz throw you.
开萝尔:
Carol: One quiz?Mom, I've been through my files.
Ten years of work, everything I've ever written, thought, or spake.
麦琪:全部都是A,我相信.
Maggie: All straight A's, I believe.
开萝尔:你刚才说过分数并不重要.
Carol: I thought you just said, grades didn't matter.
麦琪:我没说.
Maggie: I didn't.
杰森:你说了!
Jason: You did.
麦琪:对,你是问题专家,你来吧!
Maggie: Well, you're the mental health professional.Do something.
杰森:好吧,开萝尔你说下去.
Jason: Alright, Carol.Go with that.
麦琪:好.
Maggie: Oh, good.
开萝尔:我是说那些所有的 A,所有的优秀,
Carol: I mean, all those A's, all that perfect work.
其实根本不优秀,不说明任何问题.
It wasn't perfect after all!It doesn't prove a thing!
杰森:那为什么那么多老师都给你A呢?
Jason: Well, why do you think your teacher gave you all those A's?
开萝尔:就像老师给迈克D一样,
Carol: For the same reason they give Mike D's.Because it's expected.
这已经形成看法了.
Teachers know Carol Seaver gets A's.
老师们知道开萝尔总是得到A,我就是交白卷也会得A,
I mean, I can turn in a blank sheet of paper and get an A for
因为我的答案无关紧要.
being succinct.
杰森:那么你的这种声誉是怎么得的呢?
Jason: Well, how do you think you got that reputation in the first place?
开萝尔:也许是幼儿园读得好,不知道,
Carol: For having the best sand pile in kindergarten?I don't know.
我只知道前天晚上我跟Bobby出去玩,
All I do know is that I can't even fail when I admit to the teacher
没有复习功课,还照样给我一个A分.
that I didn't study because I was making out with Bobby.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
开萝尔:不过我为什么非要把他也拖到这种局面里来呢?
Carol: But then why bring him into this already tense situation?
听着我再也不惹什么麻烦了,
Look, I won't cause you any more trouble.
让我回到课堂里去争取下一个A.
Let me just go to my next class and collect my next A.
杰森:为什么?
Jason: Why?
开萝尔:什么为什么?
Carol: What do you mean why?
杰森:这么多年来驱使你努力的动力就是分数?
Jason: Well, since the thing that's been driving you all these years is
分数已经毫无意义,
getting good grades and since you've now figured out that they're worthless,
你干嘛还浪费时间,你干嘛要到课堂里去,
why waste your time?
你干嘛不回去思考?
Why even bother going to school where, God forbid, you could learn something?
开萝尔:对,现在就回家.
Carol: Good point.Let's go home.
杰森:我看能解决.
Jason: That should've worked.
开萝尔:好了本,我的甜点给你吃.
Carol: Ok, Ben.You can have my dessert.
迈克:他已经吃了.
Mike: He already ate it.
开萝尔:迈克我的心情很不好.
Carol: Mike, I'm not in a good mood.
迈克:没事,你经常这样.
Mike: Eh, it's ok.You never are.
开萝尔:迈克你要干嘛?
Carol: Mike, what do you want?
迈克:我现在进来主要是想跟你说说,
Mike: Um, well, I just came in here and wanted to say that I think it's
爸爸惩罚你是不对的.
wrong for Dad to punish you like this.
开萝尔:爸爸没有惩罚我,他是要我思考一下.
Carol: Well, Dad didn't punish me.He just sent me up here to think.
迈克:就等于是惩罚.
Mike: Sounds like punishment to me.
开萝尔:对你思考就是惩罚吗?
Carol: For you, thinking is punishment.
迈克:好家伙,我觉得你现在已经好多了开萝尔.
Mike: Hey, an insult!You know, I can tell you're feeling a lot better, Carol.
开萝尔:迈克你要干什么?
Carol: Mike, what do you want?
迈克:我不知道,我在一直跟Ben玩,
Mike: Well, I don't know,
玩的有点腻了,
I guess I just got kind of bored with just Ben to kick around,
我想你闷在房间里难受,所以来看看你.
and I sorta felt bad for you, and missed having you to harass.
开萝尔:你很好.
Carol: That's sweet.
迈克:说得非常对.
Mike: And you know, I think you're right.
开萝尔:指什么?
Carol: About what?
迈克:我是指分数并没有什么用处,
Mike: Well, you know, about grades, not meaning anything.
我一直是这个态度,分数不是看问题的.
It's always been my approach.
等我们到爸爸妈妈的年纪时,
The way I figure it is by the time we're old, like Mom and Dad,
谁来管我们的什么分数呢.
no one's really gonna care what kind of grades we got.
但我关心的是你是什么人?
All they're gonna care about is just who you are and maybe what kind of
你坐的是什么牌的汽车?你瞧你坐的别克,
car you drive.See, alright, take your Buick, now it's big,
车很大,
but what does it say?
但不够理想,
Now, you've got your Volvo, they're interesting,
要是你坐沃尔沃就好得多了,不过你手里得拿支烟斗,
but you got to be able to smoke a pipe for one of those.
或者你坐法拉利.
And you have your Ferrari, whoa!
开萝尔:等等.
Carol: Wait!
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
开萝尔:你刚才说什么?
Carol: What did you just say?
迈克:哇哦!
Mike: Whoa!
开萝尔:这句前面.
Carol: Before that.
迈克:嗯,沃尔沃.
Mike: Uh, Volvo's.
开萝尔:前面那句.
Carol: Before that.
迈克:我忘了.
Mike: I forgot.
开萝尔:你说成了大人以后,谁也不会管你学校里的分数了,
Carol: You said that when we're adults no one would care about the kind
他只关心你是什么样的人?
of grades we got in school.They'd only care about the kind of person we are.
迈克:我说了?
Mike: I said that?
开萝尔:是啊,我们越是学习,我们就会感到越加充实.
Carol: So, the more we learn the more we become enriched as people!
迈克:这句话我肯定没说.
Mike: No, I know I didn't say that!
开萝尔:哦,当然了,
Carol: Of course!Education not only shapes how other people see us but
教育不是为了塑造自己的外表,它完全是为了充实自己.
how we see ourselves.
不是为了分数,也不是为了掌握什么,
It's not about learning facts, it's not about grades,
更不是为了什么全优,而是为了做一个有价值的人.
it's not about being perfect, it's about being somebody worth knowing.
迈克:恩?
Mike: Uh-huh.
开萝尔:我要成为一个既充实又有价值的人.
Carol: I better like myself, since I'm gonna be with me all my life, right?
迈克:是吗?
Mike: Right.
开萝尔:去学校就是为了这个,这比分数还重要,这才是学习的真正的目的,这样才对,
Carol: That's worth going to school for!That's better than grades!
谢谢你迈克.妈妈,爸爸.
That's worth studying for until you drop!That's it!Thank you, Mike!Mom!Dad!
迈克:我觉得她的确理解错了.
Mike: Should've known she'd miss the point.
Maggie: So, you're saying that by sending Carol to her room to think last
就解决问题了?
night, you solved her problem?
杰森:照我的经验,已经把开萝尔真正引导向思考了,
Jason: Well, I think it's obvious that my suggestions got Carol on the
是不是我对自己的评价太那个.
road to Why?Do you think I'm taking too much credit?
麦琪:我也没说.
Maggie: Oh, I didn't say that.
杰森:我能听出你的意思麦琪.
Jason: Oh, ok.Well, it certainly sounded as maybe
本:嗨!谁把开萝尔的甜食吃了?
Ben: Hey!Who the heck ate Carol's dessert?
麦琪:开萝尔,她现在心情很好,
Maggie: Carol.She's feeling like herself again,
胃口也恢复了.本:我倒是希望她的生活毫无意义.
she even got her appetite back.
00:22:26,100
Ben: I liked it better when her life was a meaningless void.